

CONTACT DETAILS

- wicbelova.com
- © Wroclaw, Poland
- @ vacova1988@gmail.com
- (+48 452 398 093









SKILLS

- excellent work organization
- scrupulity and responsibility
- communication skills
- ability to work in a team
- knowledge of MS Office

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Polish language: level B2+
- Russian language: native
- English language: level A2

Victoria Belova

Accountant

I am an independent accountant with 5 years of experience in accounting and 8 years of experience in the field of taxation, both acquired in Belarus. Currently, I am expanding my professional competencies in Poland by regularly participating in courses and training sessions, and keeping up to date with the latest regulatory changes.

EXPERIENCE

2017-2021, 2023-2024

PhotoCeramics company, Belarus

Accountant

- ensuring proper document circulation;
- maintaining accounting records and reconciling them with general ledger accounts;
- making payments and managing the organization's current accounts;
- controlling settlements with suppliers and customerss;
- keeping records of accounting costs, reconciling them with general ledger accounts;
- maintaining revenue records for accounting and tax purposes;
- maintaining cash operations records;
- maintaining accounting cost records and reconciling them with general ledger accounts;
- accounting for costs, including for tax purposes;
- preparing financial statements (balance sheet, profit and loss statement);
- preparing statistical reports;
- calculating taxes (VAT, CIT, PIT);
- preparing and submitting tax declarations (VAT, CIT, PIT);
- cooperating with external institutions (tax office, Social Insurance Institution, others);
- working with the electronic invoice system;
- conducting inventory of current assets, fixed assets, liabilities;
- recording fixed assets;
- payroll calculation.

2009-2017, 2021-2022

Tax office, department of control over legal entities, Belarus
Tax inspector

• conducting tax audits of legal entities;

- checking organizations compliance with tax and accounting regulations;
- control of the completeness of reflection of the organization's revenues in accounting and tax reports;
- verifying the legality of including the organization's expenses as costs included for tax purposes;
- checking the correctness of tax settlements by organizations (VAT, personal and corporate income tax, land tax, real estate tax).

ADDITIONAL COURSES

2024 - currently undergoing training

Association of Accountants of Poland

speciality: Senior Accountant

2023-2024

Association of Accountants of Poland

speciality: Accountant

2013

Association of Accountants of Belarus

speciality: Accountant





EDUCATION

2004-2009

Francisk Skorina Gomel State University

speciality: economics

INTERESTS

Gym, reading, healthy lifestyle, development of personal and professional qualities

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruiting for the position I am applying for.

Victoria Belova